play the chaos game in a regular hexagon
we apply an iterative algorithm with a
random component start with a DOT
anywhere in the interior of the polygon
and then iteratively add a new Point
two-thirds of the distance between the
current dot and a uniformly randomly
chosen vertex on the hexagon you can
think of rolling a fair six-sided die
and then moving two-thirds of the way
from the dot you're currently at to the
vertex corresponding to the die roll
here's the amazing shape that arises
after applying this process 35
000 times no matter the original Point
location or the random outcomes of the
dice rolls along the way the limiting
shape that you see here is always the
limiting shape that results from this
process